sbstransit.com.sg 2013-05-01

# Welcome to SBS Transit

SBS Transit Ltd ("we" and "us", as the case may be) takes the privacy of our users seriously. More about our privacy policy is stated below: 

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect from you when you subscribe or register for online access and email updates. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage.

**Collection and Usage of Information**

• | We collect personally identifiable information when you register at our website.  
---|---  
• | When you subscribe with us, we ask for your name, mobile contact number, fare card number, email address and other personal information. Once you subscribe with us, you are not anonymous to us.  
• | We shall use the information collected for the following purposes: to notify you if there are updates on the services you have subscribed/registered for. However, SBS Transit shall at no time be held responsible or liable in any way for the loss, theft or other disclosure of the said information.  
• | We will not sell your personally identifiable information to anyone.  
• |  We will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:  
  |  | o  | We have your consent to share the information; or  
---|---  
o  | We respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process or are otherwise obligated to respond by law, or any relevant authority or regulatory body.  
• | You have the ability to edit your subscription information at any time.  
• | We may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting an announcement on the bus services time table web page. You agree that such posting will constitute sufficient and adequate notice to you of the changes. You agree that your continued use of your registration account after such amendment will constitute your acceptance of and agreement to be bound by the modified policy.
